<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<params>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    <param data-view="heading">
    We Build Digital
    </param>
    <param data-view="main_p1">
=======
    <param data-view="HOME_HEADING">
    We Build Digital
    </param>
    <param data-view="HOME_INTRO">
>>>>>>> 5867a93 (done)
        <![CDATA[
            Welcome to cmcintosh.net! I’m Christopher McIntosh, 
            a seasoned Full Stack Developer with over 15 years of 
            experience navigating the ever-evolving world of technology. 
            My journey has equipped me with a profound understanding 
            of digital solutions, ranging from web applications to 
            computer and network repair.
<<<<<<< HEAD
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="main_p2">
        <![CDATA[
=======
>>>>>>> 5867a93 (done)
            If you’re a coder, explore my current projects for inspiration. 
            Potential employers can view the web version of my resume, 
            showcasing my professional journey. 
            And if you’re in need of a custom web application, expert consulting, 
            or reliable computer and network repair services, 
            request a quote tailored to your needs. 
            Let’s build something extraordinary together!
        ]]>
    </param>
<<<<<<< HEAD
=======
    <param data-view="VIEW_INFO_LEFT">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3>Mobile and Desktop App Development</h3>
            <p>
            Stay ahead in the digital era with our mobile and desktop app development services. 
            We create powerful, user-friendly applications that run smoothly across all devices, ensuring your audience has the best experience 
            whether they’re on the go or at their desk. Our expertise spans both iOS and Android platforms, as well as Windows and macOS, 
            providing you with versatile and robust solutions.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </param>
        <param data-view="VIEW_INFO_CENTER">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3>Graphic Design and Branding</h3>
            <p>
                Make a lasting impression with our professional graphic design and 
                branding services. As an Adobe Certified expert, 
                I craft visually stunning and cohesive designs that resonate 
                with your target audience. From logos and marketing materials 
                to complete brand identities, we ensure your brand stands 
                out and communicates your vision effectively.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </param>
        <param data-view="VIEW_INFO_RIGHT">
        <![CDATA[
            <h3>Computer Repair and Consulting</h3>
            <p>
                Keep your systems running smoothly with our computer repair and 
                consulting services. With A+ and Network+ certifications, 
                we offer reliable solutions for all your hardware and software issues. 
                Our consulting services provide expert advice and strategies to optimize 
                your IT infrastructure, ensuring maximum efficiency and minimal 
                downtime for your business.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </param>
>>>>>>> 5867a93 (done)
</params>
   