<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<params>
    <param data-view="HOME_HEADING">
    We Build Digital
    </param>
    <param data-view="HOME_INTRO">
        <![CDATA[
            Welcome to cmcintosh.net! I’m Christopher McIntosh, 
            a seasoned Full Stack Developer with over 15 years of 
            experience navigating the ever-evolving world of technology. 
            My journey has equipped me with a profound understanding 
            of digital solutions, ranging from web applications to 
            computer and network repair.
            If you’re a coder, explore my current projects for inspiration. 
            Potential employers can view the web version of my resume, 
            showcasing my professional journey. 
            And if you’re in need of a custom web application, expert consulting, 
            or reliable computer and network repair services, 
            request a quote tailored to your needs. 
            Let’s build something extraordinary together!
        ]]>
    </param>

    <!--LEFT CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_PROJECTS_HEADING">Explore My Work</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_PROJECTS_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
            Dive into my portfolio and explore projects that showcase my technical expertise and creative problem-solving. From web applications to diagnostic tools, see the work that defines my professional journey.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_PROJECTS_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Projects</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_PROJECTS_CLICKTXT">View Projects</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->


    <!--MIDDLE CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_QUOTE_HEADING">Tailored Solutions</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_QUOTE_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
            Have a project in mind? Let’s discuss your ideas and create a solution that meets your unique needs. From consultation to delivery, I’ll guide you every step of the way.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_QUOTE_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Services/Quote</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_QUOTE_CLICKTXT"> More Info</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->

  
    <!--RIGHT CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_RESUME_HEADING">Skills and Expertise</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_RESUME_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
            Discover the skills and certifications that set me apart. Explore my resume to learn how my experience can bring value to your next project or business initiative.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_RESUME_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Resume</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_RESUME_CLICKTXT">View Resume</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->

  
</params>
   
