<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<params>
    <param data-view="SERVICES_HEADING">
    We Deliver Excellence
    </param>
    <param data-view="SERVICES_INTRO">
        <![CDATA[
            Explore a world of possibilities with our tailored services. Whether you need state-of-the-art web applications, 
            stunning visual designs, or reliable IT diagnostics, we have the expertise to bring your vision to life. 
            At cmcintosh.net, we combine innovation and dedication to deliver solutions that make a lasting impact.
            Discover the services that will take your digital presence to the next level. 
            Let’s turn your challenges into opportunities and your ideas into reality!
        ]]>
    </param>

    <!--LEFT CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_DEVEL_HEADING">Development</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DEVEL_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
        Stay ahead in the digital era with our Web Application Development services. 
        We create powerful, user-friendly applications that run smoothly across all devices, ensuring your audience has the best experience 
        whether they’re on the go or at their desk. Our expertise spans Linux, Windows and macOS, 
        providing you with versatile and robust solutions.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DEVEL_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Services/Development</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DEVEL_CLICKTXT">Get Started</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->


    <!--MIDDLE CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_DESIGN_HEADING">Design</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DESIGN_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
            Make a lasting impression with our professional graphic design and 
            branding services. We craft visually stunning and cohesive designs that resonate 
            with your target audience. From logos and marketing materials 
            to complete brand identities, we ensure your brand stands 
            out and communicates your vision effectively.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DESIGN_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Services/Design</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DESIGN_CLICKTXT"> More Info</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->

  
    <!--RIGHT CARD-->
    <param data-view="INFO_DIAG_HEADING">Diagnostics</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DIAG_INFO">
        <![CDATA[
                Keep your systems running smoothly with our computer repair and 
                consulting services. With A+ and Network+ certifications, 
                we offer reliable solutions for all your hardware and software issues. 
                Our consulting services provide expert advice and strategies to optimize 
                your IT infrastructure, ensuring maximum efficiency and minimal 
                downtime for your business.
        ]]>
    </param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DIAG_CLICKURL">?strRoute=/Services/Diagnostics</param>
    <param data-view="INFO_DIAG_CLICKTXT">Get It Fixed</param>
    <!--///////////////////////////////////-->

  
</params>
   
